Guide to the Henry Draper Image Collection MC.230
New York University Archives
- Series VIII: Fragments
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14847; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14848; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14849; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14850; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14851; Glass plate fragments (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Segments of Solar Disk?, undated; cuid14852; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Fragment (mended), undated; cuid14853; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14854; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14855; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Spectra, undated; cuid14856; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Distribution of Stars of Type M, undated; cuid14857; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14858; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14899; Glass plate fragments (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14859; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14860; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14861; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14900; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14901; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14862; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Fragment, undated; cuid14863; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Solar Spectrum?, 26 March 1879; cuid14864; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Solar Spectrum?, undated; cuid14865; Glass plate fragments (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Box of Fragments, undated; cuid14866; Glass plate fragments (Box 26)
- Series IX: Memorabilia
  - Wooden Lantern Slide Box, March 1915; cuid14867; Wooden box (Box 27)
  - Wooden Lantern Slide Box, March 1915; cuid14868; Wooden box (Box 28)
  - Wooden Lantern Slide Box, undated; cuid14869; Wooden box (Box 29)
  - Wooden cabinet that housed glass plate negatives, undated; cuid14874 (Box 40)
    ID Number: 286. Description: containing spectral slides. Creator/Donor/Subject: Draper, Henry. Dimensions: 21w x 13d x 15.5h
- Series X: Miscellaneous
  - Henry Draper Memorial (1), undated; cuid2080; Glass plate (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Henry Draper Memorial (6), undated; cuid14564; Cardboard print (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous notes, circa late 19th century; cuid14886 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Image of insect, circa late 19th century; cuid14887; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reproduction of an unidentified document, circa late 19th century; cuid14888; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reproduction of an unidentified document, circa late 19th century; cuid14894; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Illustration of superior vena cava and human head, circa late 19th century; cuid14893; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reproduction of an unidentified document "Chapter 7" (damaged), circa 1890s; cuid14895; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reproduction of an unidentified document "Chapter 7", circa 1890s; cuid14896; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reproduction of an unidentified document, circa late 19th century; cuid14897; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Reproduction of a John Johnson photograph, 1845; cuid14898; Image on paper (Box 30, Folder 10)